<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Yoga Info</string>
    <string name="trikonasana_is_performed_in_two_parts_facing_left_and_then_facing_right_the_practitioner_begins_standing_with_the_feet_one_leg_length_apart_knees_unbent_turns_the_right_foot_completely_to_the_outside_and_the_left_foot_less_than_45_degrees_to_the_inside_keeping_the_heels_in_line_with_the_hips_the_arms_are_spread_out_to_the_sides_parallel_to_the_ground_palms_facing_down_the_trunk_is_extended_as_far_as_is_comfortable_to_the_right_while_the_arms_remain_parallel_to_the_floor">Trikonasana is performed in two parts, facing left, and then facing right.The practitioner begins standing with the feet one leg-length apart, knees unbent, turns the right foot completely to the outside and the left foot less than 45 degrees to the inside, keeping the heels in line with the hips. The arms are spread out to the sides, parallel to the ground, palms facing down; the trunk is extended as far as is comfortable to the right, while the arms remain parallel to the floor.</string>
    <string name="this_stretch_spans_the_lower_middle_and_upper_back_rises_up_the_neck_and_circles_over_the_scalp_and_back_down_the_forehead_finally_ending_at_the_point_between_the_eyebrows_says_lee_when_you_fold_forward_in_uttanasana_you_stretch_this_entire_sheath_of_muscles_and_connective_tissue_from_the_fulcrum_of_the_forward_bend_the_pelvis">This [stretch] spans the lower, middle, and upper back; rises up the neck; and circles over the scalp and back down the forehead, finally ending at the point between the eyebrows,” says Lee. When you fold forward in Uttanasana, you stretch this entire sheath of muscles and connective tissue, from the fulcrum of the forward bend, the pelvis.</string>
    <string name="stand_straight_balance_firmly_on_your_left_leg_and_lift_your_right_leg_bend_your_right_leg_at_the_knee_now_place_your_right_foot_against_the_inside_of_your_left_thigh_make_sure_the_toes_of_your_right_foot_facing_downward_join_your_palms_in_prayer_at_your_chest_level_now_lift_your_arms_over_your_head_till_your_hands_are_stretched_upward_hold_the_position_while_breathing_deeply_lower_your_arms_to_chest_level_and_then_separate_your_palms_straighten_your_right_leg_and_stand_erect_again_repeat_the_posture_with_your_right_leg">Stand straight. Balance firmly on your left leg and lift your right leg. Bend your right leg at the knee. Now, place your right foot against the inside of your left thigh. Make sure the toes of your right foot facing downward. Join your palms in prayer at your chest level. Now, lift your arms over your head till your hands are stretched upward. Hold the position while breathing deeply. Lower your arms to chest level and then separate your palms. Straighten your right leg and stand erect again. Repeat the posture with your right leg.</string>
    <string name="in_the_supported_headstand_salamba_shirshasana_the_body_is_completely_inverted_and_held_upright_supported_by_the_forearms_and_the_crown_of_the_head_in_his_light_on_yoga_b_k_s_iyengar_uses_a_forearm_support_with_the_fingers_interlocked_around_the_head_for_the_basic_posture_shirshasana_i_and_its_variations_he_demonstrates_a_western_style_tripod_headstand_the_palms_of_the_hands_on_the_ground_with_raised_elbows_for_shirshasana_ii_and_iii_and_other_supports_for_further_variants_iyengar_names_and_illustrates_ten_variants_in_all_as_well_as_several_preparatory_and_transitional_poses">In the Supported Headstand (Salamba Shirshasana), the body is completely inverted, and held upright supported by the forearms and the crown of the head.[7] In his Light on Yoga, B. K. S. Iyengar uses a forearm support, with the fingers interlocked around the head, for the basic posture Shirshasana I and its variations; he demonstrates a Western-style tripod headstand, the palms of the hands on the ground with raised elbows, for Shirshasana II and III; and other supports for further variants. Iyengar names and illustrates ten variants in all, as well as several preparatory and transitional poses</string>
</resources>